

5104 Proper Tunghaan Minglanilla, Cebu 6046 **ADDRESS**

(+63) 943 221 9155 **PHONE**

johnlloydmayol@gmail.com E-MAIL

https://github.com/mayol27 **GITHUB**

www.linkedin.com/in/johnlloyd-mayol LINKEDIN

ABOUT ME

A skilled IT affluent young professional with more than 4 years of experience Software Development & Design, Hardware and Software Maintenance and Repair, and Graphics Design enhancina PHP in Programming Languages (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, W3, CSS, and PHP).

SKILLS

WORK

PHOTOSHOP ILLUSTRATOR LARAVEL CODEIGNITER PHP MYSQL HTML CSS **BOOTSTRAP**

JOHN LLOYD SEGISMAR MAYOL

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

EXPERIENCE

(October 2019)

Devcash

THESIS

A SOFTWARE-AS-A-SERVICE FOR CASHIERING SYSTEM FOR MICRO AND **SMALL ENTERPRISES**

Position: Hipster

Language: Angular.js, PHP, Bootstrap, CSS, HTML, Android, and Firebase (June 2015 – October 2019)

WORKING SCHOLAR - UNIVERSITY OF CEBU

LABORATORY ASSISTANT

- + Technical Support for computer laboratory
- + Assisting students and teachers on computer laboratory
- + Sorting and filing documents

(October 2018 - May 2019)

ON-THE JOB TRAINIG - KREDO IT ABROD INC.

PROGRAMMER

- + Technical Support for computer
- + Created Inventory System for the company

EDUCATION

(June 2015 - October 2019)

University of Cebu – Main Campus

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

(June 2011 - March 2015)

Immaculate Heart of Mary Academy – Minglanilla HIGH SCHOOL

ORGANIZATION

(March 2017 – Present)

GDG Cebu - Google Developers Group

(April 2015 – October 2019)

UNIVERSITY OF CEBU - ASSOCIATION OF WORKING SCHOLARS (AWS)

(June 2015 – October 2019)

UNIVERSITY OF CEBU - PHILIPPINE SOCIETY OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY STUDENT (PSITS)

CERTIFICATES

Building Entrepreneurial Ecosystem to Enhance Higher Education Value-Added for Better Graduate Employability (BEEHIVE) -MOOC

(2017)

5th UC-ICT Congress "Sharpening Junior Mobile Technologists"

(2016)

4th UC-ICT Congress "Shaping up Creative Minds through Great **UX Design**"

С C++

TROUBLESHOOT

PERSONAL

COMMUNICATION ORGANIZATION TEAM PLAYER CREATIVITY SOCIAL

REFERENCE

Ms. Ma. Catherine Carumba

Secretary – College of Computer Studies

Contact: 255 – 7777 loc. 113

Ms. Lina J. Perez

UCEMPC - Secretary Contact: 255 – 7777 loc. 136 Ms. Jerrah Marie Son

Laboratory Supervisor – CCS Contact: 0923 – 866 – 7880